<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>BAPC21 Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam</title><link>https://bapc21.storm.vu/</link><description>Recent content on BAPC21 Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://bapc21.storm.vu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Jury/CfP</title><link>https://bapc21.storm.vu/jury/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:41:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://bapc21.storm.vu/jury/</guid><description>Jury Call for Problems The call for problems (CfP) can be found at jury.bapc.eu. The jury creates the problem set for both the BAPC preliminaries and the BAPC 2021. For questions, please check the Slack for more information.
The deadline for submitting problems to this CfP is March 14th 2021.</description></item><item><title>Schedule</title><link>https://bapc21.storm.vu/schedule/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:41:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://bapc21.storm.vu/schedule/</guid><description>Schedule The schedule of the day itself is still uncertain. The schedule of this year looks something like this:
Month 04, discussion with other associations on when the preliminaries can be held (organized by individual universities). Month 06, possibly preliminaries Month 09, the preliminaries Month 10, BAPC21 This planning is subject to change as the Benelux still faces problems with COVID-19.</description></item><item><title>Registration</title><link>https://bapc21.storm.vu/registration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:41:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://bapc21.storm.vu/registration/</guid><description>Registration The registration will be opened after the preliminaries has finished. The preliminaries are expected to be held in the summer of 2021.
Signing up for a preliminary at your institution is independent of a registration for BAPC21. Info on how to register a team representing your own university/school is often arranged via your teaching staff or the study association representing either the math or computer science department.</description></item><item><title>On-site Contest</title><link>https://bapc21.storm.vu/contest_offline/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:41:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://bapc21.storm.vu/contest_offline/</guid><description>Contest VU Amsterdam Campus Due to COVID-19 measures, we don&amp;rsquo;t know this yet. We are working on both plans (on-site and online) and will inform you as soon as possible. Possible ideas have been pitched in April to the other institutions.</description></item><item><title>Online Contest</title><link>https://bapc21.storm.vu/contest_online/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:41:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://bapc21.storm.vu/contest_online/</guid><description>Contest Online Due to COVID-19 measures, we don&amp;rsquo;t know this yet. We are working on both plans (on-site and online) and will inform you as soon as possible. Possible ideas have been pitched in April to the other institutions.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://bapc21.storm.vu/contact/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:41:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://bapc21.storm.vu/contact/</guid><description>Contact If you have any questions or want to the contact the 2021 BAPC committee, please drop us an email at: organization “at” BAPC “dot” EU (not active yet).
Sponsoring Companies interested in supporting the contest or participating as a company team, can email us at: Claudia “at” STORM “dot” VU.
Jury The Call for Problems is open for both problems and jury members. For questions see the information at the Jury site.</description></item></channel></rss>