<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>BAPC21 - Benelux Algorithm Programming Contest</title><link>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/</link><description>Recent content on BAPC21 - Benelux Algorithm Programming Contest</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Jury</title><link>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/jury/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:41:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/jury/</guid><description>Jury The Call for Problems for BAPC 2021 has ended.
The BAPC 2021 jury consists of, in alphabetical order,
Erik Baalhuis Ruben Brokkelkamp Ragnar Groot Koerkamp Joey Haas Freek Henstra Boas Kluiving Timon Knigge Ludo Pulles Reinier Schmiermann Maarten Sijm Harry Smit Jorke de Vlas Mees de Vries Wessel van Woerden</description></item><item><title>Schedule</title><link>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/schedule/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:41:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/schedule/</guid><description>Schedule The schedule of the day itself is still uncertain. The schedule of this year looks something like this:
Date Action 19 September Update on Online/Offline planning of BAPC2021 9 October BAPC preliminaries (organized by individual universities) 13 October First round of slot allocations 30 October BAPC 2021 This planning is subject to change as the Benelux still faces problems with COVID-19.</description></item><item><title>Registration</title><link>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/registration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:41:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/registration/</guid><description>Registration The registration will open after the preliminaries have taken place.
Preliminaries The slots per institution for BAPC21 are limited. As there tends to be more teams than slots available, your institution can hold preliminary contests to determine which teams qualify for BAPC21. The preliminaries will hold on Saturday, 9 October.
Registration for a preliminary at your institution is independent of a registration for BAPC21. Information on how to register a team representing your university is often arranged via your teaching staff or the study association representing either the mathematics or computer science department.</description></item><item><title>Contest</title><link>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/contest/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:41:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/contest/</guid><description>Contest Due to COVID-19 measures, it&amp;rsquo;s unclear whether we will be able to hold an on-site contest at the VU Amsterdam campus. We are working on both on-site and online contests and will inform you as soon as possible. Ideas have been pitched in April to the other institutions.</description></item><item><title>Rules</title><link>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/rules/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:41:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/rules/</guid><description>Rules These rules and the chosen format may change depending on the measures for the COVID-19 pandemic.
General Rules Definitions BAPC: The Benelux Algorithm Programming Contest 2021. Hosted by the Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam. Organization: The members of the organizing committee. Website: The website, maintained by the organization and available at 2021.bapc.eu. Slack: The BAPC Slack workspace mentioned in Contact. Jury: The group responsible for creating the problem set and checking the solutions submitted by the participants.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/contact/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:41:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/contact/</guid><description>Contact The BAPC 2021 is hosted by Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam, and organized by a committee of study association STORM. If you have any questions or want to contact the BAPC 2021 committee, these are the ways to do it (in order of preference):
Slack — The BAPC community maintains a Slack. Feel free to reach out to us on the #general channel in the Slack. For access, visit this link with token I heart Benelux.</description></item><item><title>Help us</title><link>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/eventcrew/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:41:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/eventcrew/</guid><description>Call for Volunteers If you want to help us during the BAPC, please fill in this form.</description></item><item><title>Special thanks</title><link>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/thanks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:41:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/thanks/</guid><description>Community sponsors We thank Thijs at SURF for providing DNS help with the bapc.eu. We use DOMjudge Creative commons: We use the following comics in our logo from xkcd: 1011: Baby Names 1081: Argument Victory 1106: ADD</description></item></channel></rss>