<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>BAPC21 - Benelux Algorithm Programming Contest</title><link>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/</link><description>Recent content on BAPC21 - Benelux Algorithm Programming Contest</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Jury</title><link>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/jury/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:41:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/jury/</guid><description>Jury The Call for Problems for BAPC 2021 has ended.
The BAPC 2021 jury consists of, in alphabetical order,
Erik Baalhuis Ruben Brokkelkamp Ragnar Groot Koerkamp Joey Haas Freek Henstra Boas Kluiving Timon Knigge Ludo Pulles Reinier Schmiermann Maarten Sijm Harry Smit Jorke de Vlas Mees de Vries Wessel van Woerden</description></item><item><title>Schedule</title><link>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/dayschedule/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:41:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/dayschedule/</guid><description>Schedule Start End Event 09:00 10:00 Reception and registration (per team) 10:00 10:30 Welcome and introductory remarks 11:00 12:00 Test session 12:00 13:00 Lunch, sponsor meetup, last remarks 13:00 18:00 Contest 15:00 16:00 Coaches meeting 18:00 Drinks 18:00 19:30 Jury solutions 19:30 21:00 Award ceremony</description></item><item><title>Photos</title><link>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/photos/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:41:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/photos/</guid><description>Photos Pictures will be available soon. We&amp;rsquo;re currently in the process of the after effects.
The current planning is next week.</description></item><item><title>Registration</title><link>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/registration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:41:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/registration/</guid><description>Registration The registration has now closed. Teams will be informed of whether they have been accepted and any relevant information will be sent to the accepted teams at a later date.
Preliminaries The slots per institution for BAPC21 are limited. As there tends to be more teams than slots available, your institution can hold preliminary contests to determine which teams qualify for BAPC21. Most preliminaries will hold on Saturday, 9 October.</description></item><item><title>Location</title><link>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/contest/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:41:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/contest/</guid><description>Location The event will be held on the VU Amsterdam campus. The team reception and registration will take place in the TenT building, and the rest of the activities of the day will take place in the Nieuwe Universiteitgebouw (the NU building). For general information on how to reach the campus, please visit the route description.</description></item><item><title>Rules</title><link>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/rules/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:41:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/rules/</guid><description>Rules These rules and the chosen format may change depending on the measures for the COVID-19 pandemic.
General Rules Definitions BAPC: The Benelux Algorithm Programming Contest 2021. Hosted by the Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam. Organization: The members of the organizing committee. Website: The website, maintained by the organization and available at 2021.bapc.eu. Slack: The BAPC Slack workspace mentioned in Contact. Jury: The group responsible for creating the problem set and checking the solutions submitted by the participants.</description></item><item><title>Help us</title><link>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/eventcrew/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:41:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/eventcrew/</guid><description>Call for Volunteers If you want to help us during the BAPC, please fill in this form.</description></item><item><title>Company teams</title><link>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/companycup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:41:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/companycup/</guid><description>Company teams</description></item><item><title>Special thanks</title><link>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/thanks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:41:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/thanks/</guid><description>Community sponsors We thank Thijs at SURF for providing DNS help with the bapc.eu. We use DOMjudge We use ICPC-Tools Creative commons: We use the following comics in our logo from xkcd: 1011: Baby Names 1081: Argument Victory 1106: ADD University We thank Alexandru/A. Iosup</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/contact/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:41:52 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://studieverenigingstorm.github.io/BAPC21-site/contact/</guid><description>Contact The BAPC 2021 is hosted by Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam, and organized by a committee of study association STORM. If you have any questions or want to contact the BAPC 2021 committee, these are the ways to do it (in order of preference):
Slack — The BAPC community maintains a Slack. Feel free to reach out to us on the #general channel in the Slack. For access, visit this link with token I heart Benelux.</description></item></channel></rss>